<project3>
    <iconImg>/projectData/img/project3/icon.png</iconImg>
    <title>AI-Learners Special Needs Children's Learning Platform</title>
    <dateCompleted>Summer 2020</dateCompleted>
    <projectLanguages>Typescript, NoSQL (Firebase), Python</projectLanguages>
    <productionURL>https://ai-learners.com/</productionURL>



    <backgroundTitle>Background</backgroundTitle>
    <backgroundDesc>
    The founder, Adele, had created a post on Cornell University's subreddit looking for other Cornell students to help her develop a
    learning platform for special needs children. I was interested in the project and reached out to her. We had a meeting and I
    was brought on to the team. The platform was to be a web application that would use machine learning to help children learn
    better. The platform would be able to detect the child's emotions and adjust the learning material accordingly. The project
    was worked on by myself and 3 other students. I was a lead developer at the time and was responsible for improving the 
    front-end and back-end. The project eventually gained even more traction after I left and became a fully funded startup by
    Cornell e-labs and Life Changing Labs. Here is a video of the project: https://youtu.be/fVuSQQCCumA
    </backgroundDesc>
    <backgroundImg>/projectData/img/project3/background.png</backgroundImg>
    <backgroundImgDesc>Here is the home page of the website. Visitors can try out demo games and read more about it.</backgroundImgDesc>

    <learnedTitle>What I learned</learnedTitle>
    <learnedPts>
        <pts>How to lead a project team with other students</pts>
        <pts>End to end software development</pts>
        <pts>Applications of NoSQL database systems</pts>
        <pts>Fine tuning machine learning models using customized data sets</pts>
    </learnedPts>

    <section>
        <title>Project Media</title>

        <img>
            <path>/projectData/img/project3/avatar_creation.png</path>
            <desc>
                Users are able to create their own avatars to make the learning experience more personal.
            </desc>
        </img>

        <img>
            <path>/projectData/img/project3/different_game_options.png</path>
            <desc>
                Here are some of the games that the platform offers. Each game is designed to help children learn in a different way.
            </desc>
        </img>

        <img>
            <path>/projectData/img/project3/pregame_selection.png</path>
            <desc>
                Accessability features are available for children with different needs.
            </desc>
        </img>
    </section>
</project3>