<project3>
    <iconImg>/projectData/img/project1/assign_logo.png</iconImg>
    <title>AI-Learners Learn Platform Full Stack Web Application</title>
    <dateCompleted>May 2019</dateCompleted>
    <projectLanguages>Python, Kivy</projectLanguages>
    <productionURL>https://github.com/anthonyjdearmas/Job-Assigner</productionURL>



    <backgroundTitle>Background</backgroundTitle>
    <backgroundDesc>
    This is my first project! At the time, my dorm had a house manager posistion that was in charge of assigning weekly jobs
    to all of the house mates. I would find the house manager spending a lot of his time on assigning jobs. I knew he
    could get the job done quicker if he had the right tool. As a result, I decided to use what I learned from my first
    Computer Science course at Cornell and design a job assigner program using Python. The house manager was able to use
    my program to quickly generate job assignments and save himself plenty of time to do other things!
    </backgroundDesc>
    <backgroundImg>/projectData/img/project1/main_menu.png</backgroundImg>
    <backgroundImgDesc>The main menu of the application. You can either configure settings, go to my GitHub or create job assignments here.</backgroundImgDesc>

    <learnedTitle>What I learned</learnedTitle>
    <learnedPts>
        <pts>How to create a GUI using Kivy and Python</pts>
        <pts>Basic data management</pts>
        <pts>Applications of important data structures (lists and dictionaries)</pts>
        <pts>Threading</pts>
    </learnedPts>

    <section>
        <title>Project Media</title>

        <img>
            <path>/projectData/img/project1/config_page.png</path>
            <desc>
                Here is an example of what it is like to add or remove a person. The same happens for a job!
            </desc>
        </img>

        <img>
            <path>/projectData/img/project1/add_element.png</path>
            <desc>
                Job Description: Modify his existing code to add a skill system that allows players to level up and gain new abilities.
            </desc>
        </img>

        <img>
            <path>/projectData/img/project1/excl_expt.png</path>
            <desc>
                Here are what exported assignments look like.
            </desc>
        </img>
    </section>
</project3>