<project6>
    <iconImg>/projectData/img/project6/icon.png</iconImg>
    <title>Advanced Webscraper for Food Business Data</title>
    <dateCompleted>December 2024</dateCompleted>
    <projectLanguages>Python, Selenium</projectLanguages>
    <githubURL>https://github.com/anthonyjdearmas/pa_business_webscraper</githubURL>



    <backgroundTitle>Background</backgroundTitle>
    <backgroundDesc>
    With SafeServe Metro completed, I thought it would be a good idea to create a webscraper that would gather data from Pennsylvania's
    Department of Agriculture's website to see which busineses have an expired food safety certificate. This would help connect customer's who
    are in need of a food safety certificate with the website that I created. However, the website uses Microsoft's ASP.NET framework which makes
    it difficult to scrape data from. I had to use Selenium to automate the process of clicking through the website and gathering the data.
    In addition, the only way to determine if a company has an expired certificate is to analyze the inspectors' comments. Each inspector uses
    different wording to describe an expired certificate. To get around this I created a small dictionary of REGEX expressions that would
    match the inspector's comments to determine if a company has an expired certificate. The program is fully configurable to make it easy
    for anyone to run it. You can choose the time frame to scrape from along with which counties you want to scrape. With this, I was able 
    to gather data from over 500 businesses in Pennsylvania and determine which ones have an expired certificate.
    </backgroundDesc>
    <backgroundImg></backgroundImg>
    <backgroundImgDesc></backgroundImgDesc>

    <learnedTitle>What I learned</learnedTitle>
    <learnedPts>
        <pts>How data is processed in ASP .NET web applications</pts>
        <pts>Advanced web scraping techniques</pts>
        <pts>Synchronization</pts>
        <pts>Pattern recognition using REGEX</pts>
    </learnedPts>

    <section>
        <title>Project Media</title>

        <mp4>
            <path>/projectData/img/project6/scraper_demo.mp4</path>
            <desc>
                Here is a demo of the webscraper in action. It is fully automated and can be configured to scrape any county in Pennsylvania.
            </desc>
        </mp4>

        <img>
            <path>/projectData/img/project6/patterns.png</path>
            <desc>
                The patterns that I used to determine if a company has an expired certificate.
            </desc>
        </img>
    </section>
</project6>