<project1>
    <iconImg>/projectData/img/project1/icon_img.png</iconImg>
    <title>GmodStore Job Notifier</title>
    <dateCompleted>2018-01-01</dateCompleted>
    <projectLanguages>Java, HTML, CSS, Lua</projectLanguages>
    <githubURL>https://github.com/anthonyjdearmas/GmodStore-Job-Notifer</githubURL>



    <backgroundTitle>Background</backgroundTitle>
    <backgroundDesc>
    Garry's Mod is a popular sandbox computer game that was created in 2004. In the game, people are able to create servers with various 
    mods using the Lua programming language. Many users want to make new mods for their friends and themselves to enjoy, but are not sure 
    how to code. This is why the Garry's Mod script market place, https://www.gmodstore.com , was founded. Through the market place, people 
    who want a mod to be made can post a job listing for a freelance developer, such as myself, to apply. However, developers need to be quick 
    to see the new jobs and apply because you compete with other developers. I would find myself missing out on a lot of jobs I would like 
    to do because I was not refreshing the page every 5 minutes to see new listings. So I decided to create a Java web-scraping program that
     will automatically notify me of new jobs!
    </backgroundDesc>
    <backgroundImg>/projectData/img/project1/gmodnotifier_app.png</backgroundImg>
    <backgroundImgDesc>The GmodStore job notifier that I created to be able to apply to more jobs.</backgroundImgDesc>

    <learnedTitle>What I learned</learnedTitle>
    <learnedPts>
        <pts>How to efficently web scrape a website for information via JSoup</pts>
        <pts>Java-based GUI development via JSwing</pts>
        <pts>Synchronization</pts>
        <pts>Netlibrary usage (Lua)</pts>
        <pts>HUD design (Lua)</pts>
        <pts>Client communication and interaction</pts>
    </learnedPts>

    <section>
        <title>Project Media</title>

        <img>
            <path>/projectData/img/project1/ex_job2.jpg</path>
            <desc>
            Job Description: Turn my prop model into flyable entity that players can drive. Planes must also be able to drop bombs and carry 8 passengers inside.
            </desc>
        </img>

        <img>
            <path>/projectData/img/project1/ex_job3.png</path>
            <desc>
            Job Description: Modify his existing code to add a skill system that allows players to level up and gain new abilities.
            </desc>
        </img>
    </section>

    <section>
        <title>Jobs I completed</title>

        <img>
            <path>/projectData/img/project1/gmodstore_rep.png</path>
            <desc>Here are some of my client reviews!</desc>
        </img>
    </section>



</project1>